<resources>
    <string name="app_name">GoFitness</string>
    <string name="lets_workout_today">Let’s workout today</string>
    <string name="manage_your_own_workout">Manage Your Own Workout</string>
    <string name="important_nutrition">Nutrition is important for you</string>
    <string name="broader_view">Have a Broader View</string>
    <string name="start_workout_today">Start workout today with GoFitness</string>
    <string name="planning_and_tracking">Planning, managing and tracking  your own workout activities</string>
    <string name="help_recommend_diet">GoFitness help recommend you the best diet based on your workout goal</string>
    <string name="statistic_will_help">Statistic will help you get all information you need about your workout</string>
    <string name="underweight">This prove that you\'re below the healthy range for one\'s height, which may indicate insufficient body weight relative to height
        and can be associated with potential health concerns, such as weakened immunity and nutrient deficiencies.</string>
    <string name="normal_weight">This BMI falls within the healthy range for your height, it indicates that your weight is in proportion to your stature,
        which is generally linked to a lower risk of health issues like heart disease and diabetes for you as an individual.</string>
    <string name="overweight">When your body exceeds the recommended healthy weight range for your height, it signifies that you carry excess weight relative to your stature,
        potentially increasing the risk of health issues such as heart disease, hypertension, and joint problems for you personally.</string>
    <string name="obeseI"> it means you Obese I you have a significant excess of body weight compared to your height,
        which can elevate your personal risk for a range of health conditions including diabetes, sleep apnea, and cardiovascular diseases.</string>
    <string name="obeseII"> This indicates a substantial excess of body weight relative to your height,
        putting you at a higher personal risk for serious health issues like type 2 diabetes, heart disease, and joint problems.</string>
    <string name="obeseIII">This signifies a severe excess of body weight compared to your height,
        posing a significant personal risk for severe health conditions, including heart disease, stroke, certain cancers, and mobility limitations.</string>
</resources>